Inventaris van het archief van het Rijksinstituut voor Oorlogsdocumentatie (RIOD), 1933-1966
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- NAOORLOGS ARCHIEF 1945 t/m 1966, B
  - ALGEMENE DOCUMENTEN EN VERTAALDE DOCUMENTEN, GEBRUIKT BIJ DE PROCESSEN TE NEURENBERG., 45.
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1107
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1108
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1109
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1110
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1111
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1112
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1113
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1114
    - Diverse vertaalde documenten van de office of U.S. Chief of Counsel., 1115
  - PROCESSEN NEURENBERG BIJ HET INTERNATIONAL MILITARY TRIBUNAL AGAINST GORING EN ANDEREN., 46.
    - Closing brief against Bormans. 31 juli 1946, Closing arguments for Martin Bormans before teh IMT, Nürnberg at the trial against Hermann Göring et al.by Dr. Friedrich Bergold. 1946; 1116
    - Documentbook I, II, III en IV i/z Karl Dönitz., 1117
    - Closing brief against Karl Dönitz., 31 juli 1946; 1118
    - Gecopieëerde brief aan het IMT i/z Dr. Hans Frank for war crimes et al., 26 febr. 1946; 1119
    - Closing brief against H. Frank., 31 juli 1946; 1120
    - Closin brief against Wilhelm Frick, 31 juli 1946; 1121
    - Documentbook I over H. Fritzsche, 1122
    - List of witnesses and provisional list of documents i/z Hans Fritzsche, 1123
    - Verdedigingsschema's Fritzsche., 1124
    - Closing brief against Hans Fritzsche. Vertaling van doument PS-2976., 31 juli 1946; 1125
    - Index of documents and witnesses en translation of document i/z Walter Funk., 1126
    - Verdedigingsschema's voor Walter Funk., 1127
    - Closing brief against Walter Funk., 31 juli 1946; 1128
    - Documentbook Hermann Göring, 1129
    - Closing brief against Hermann Göring; Documentbook in de zaak tegen Göring; Trialbrief Göring; Exhibit Göring no. 23 en no. 45., 31 juli 1946; 1130
    - Documentbook i/z Rudolf Hess., 1131
    - Closing brief against Rudolf Hess., 31 juli 1946; 1132
    - Verdediging Jodi., 1 maart 1946; 1133
    - Closing brief against Jodl., 31 juli 1946; 1134
    - Closing brief against Ernst Kaltenbrunner., 31 juli 1946; 1135
    - Closing brief against Keitel, 31 juli 1946; 1136
    - Affidativ Dr. Mildner, 30 mrt. 1946; 1137
    - List of documents i/z von Neurath, 1138
    - Closing brief against Constantin von Neurath., 31 juli 1946; 1139
    - Presentation of Evidence i/z Franz von Papen., 1140
    - Closing brief against Frans von Papen, 31 juli 1946; 1141
    - Decumentbooks I t/m IV i/z Erich Räder., 1946; 1142
    - Organisatie van het proces i/z Erich Räder., 1143
    - Closing brief against Erich Räder., 31 juli 1946; 1144
    - The documents submitted for the Joachim von Ribbentrop documentbook in the order in which they are required for the presentation of the evidence., 1946; 1145
    - Closing brief against Joachim von Ribbentrop., 31 juli 1946; 1146
    - IMT, Ministère public français: stukken m.b.t. Official Defense Counsel en requisitoire individuel contre Alfred Rosenberg., jan. 1946; 1147
    - Closing brief against Alfred Rosenberg., 31 juli 1946; 1148
    - Decumentbook for the defendant Fritz Sauckel., 1946; 1149
    - Closing brief against Fritz Sauckel., 31 juli 1946; 1150
    - Closing brief against H. Schacht., 31 juli 1946; 1151
    - Documentbook for the defendant Baldur von Schirach., 1946; 1152
    - Closing brief; against B. von Schirach. 31 juli 1946, Document: the case of B. von Schirach. 24 juni 1946; 1153
    - Documentbook; defense exhibits I t/m III en trial brief i/z Arthur Seyss-Inquart; Gesprekken met Frau Gertrud Seyss-Inquart., 30 sept. 1932; 1154
    - Documentbook on Seyss-Inquart en Defense Exhibits nos. 1 t/m 87., 1946; 1155
    - Fotocopieën van een brief van Seyss-In-quart aan Martin Bormann., 22 febr. 1944; 1156
    - Defense Exhibit nr. 105 i/z Dr. Seyss-Inquart., 1946; 1157
    - Verdedigingsschema's Seyss-Inquart., 1158
    - List of Witnesses and documents for the defendant Albert Speer., 1159
    - Closing brief against A. Speer., 31 juli 1946; 1160
    - Documenten i/z Julius Streicher., 1161
    - Vertaald document i/z Julius Streicher., 1162
    - Document i/z redevoeringen van Streicher, 1163
    - List of witnesses and documents for the defendant J. Streicher., 1164
    - Closing brief against Julius Streicher., 31 juli 1946; 1165
    - Zittingen van het IMT in het proces contra H.W. Göring e.a., 12, 20 en 21 nov. 1945; 1166
    - Zittingen van het IMT in het proces contra H.W. Göring e.a., 18 t/m 28-01-1946; 1167
    - Zittingen van het IMT in het proces contra H.W. Göring e.a., 30-01-1946 t/m 05-02-1946; 1168
    - Zittingen van het IMT in het proces contra H.W. Göring e.a., 07-03-1946 t/m 21-03-1946; 1169
    - Zittingen van het IMT in het proces contra H.W. Göring e.a., 22-03-1946 t/m 06-04-1946; 1170
    - Zittingen van het IMT in het proces contra H.W. Göring e.a., 08-04-1946 t/m 16-04-1946; 1171
    - Zittingen van het IMT in het proces contra H.W. Göring e.a., 17-04-1946 t/m 01-10-1946; 1172
    - Zittingen van het IMT in het proces contra H.W. Göring e.a., 11, 14 juni 1946; 1173
  - PROCESSEN NEURENBERG, AMERICAN MILITARY TRIBUNAL, 47.
    - A.M.T. Court 1 case 1, against Karl Brandt e.a., 47.1.
      - Indictment; openingsrede door Dr. Gustav Steinbauer voor prof. Dr. Wihelm Beiglbück., 13 dec. 1946; 1174
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 9-12-1946 t/m 17-12-1946; 1175
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 18-12-1946 t/m 10-01-1947; 1176
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 13-01-1947 t/m 16-01-1947; 1177
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 17-01-1947 t/m 03-02-1947; 1178
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 04-02-1947 t/m 19-02-1947; 1179
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 20-02-1947 t/m 26-02-1947; 1180
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 27-02-1947 t/m 5-03-1947; 1181
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 06-03-1947 t/m 21-03-1947; 1182
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 24-03-1947 t/m 09-04-1947; 1183
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 10-04-1947 t/m 18-04-1947; 1184
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 21-04-1947 t/m 25-04-1947; 1185
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 28-04-1947 t/m 09-05-1947; 1186
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 12-05-1947 t/m 27-05-1947; 1187
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 28-05-1947 t/m 12-06-1947; 1188
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 13-06-1947 t/m 18-06-1947; 1189
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 19-06-1947 t/m 24-06-1947; 1190
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 25-06-1947 t/m 14-07-1947; 1191
      - Official transcripts of the AMT court I of the U.S.A. against Karl Brandt,et al, defendants, zitting at Nürnberg, Germany. (vonnissen)., 15-07-1947 t/m 20-aug.1947; 1192
    - A.M.T. Court 1, case VIII against Ulrich Greifert e.a., 47.2.
      - Documentbook i/z Ulrich Greifeit., 1193
      - Indictments; openingsrede voor Ulrich Greifeit; Closing brief voor Richard Hildebrandt; febr. 1948, pleidooi voor Richard Hildebrandt; openingsrede voor Herbert Hübner; 20 nov. 1947; pleidooi voor Herbert Hübner; openingsrede voor prof. Dr. Konrad Meyer-Hetling; 11 febr. 1948; pleidooi voor Konrad Meyer-Hetling. febr. 1948; pleidooi voor Fritz Schwalm. febr. 1948; pleidoor voor Otto Schwarzenberger. febr. 1948; [1947, 1948]; 1194
      - Zittingen van AMT court I in case VIII 20 okt. 1947, contra Ulrich Greifeit e.a. 10 mrt. 1948; [1947, 1948]; 1195
    - A.M.T. Court 2, case II against Erhard Milch e.a., 47.3.
      - Indichment; concerning opinion; Zittingen in de zaak tegen Erhard Milch., 16, 17 apr. 1947; 1196
    - A.M.T. Court 2, case IV against Oswald Pohl e.a., 47.4.
      - Indictment; documentenboek on Dr. Hans Bobermin., 1197
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 10-03-1947 t/m 16-04-1947; 1198
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 17-04-1947 t/m 20-05-1947; 1199
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 21-05-1947 t/m 05-06-1947; 1200
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 06-06-1947 t/m 20-06-1947; 1201
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 23-06-1947 t/m 30-06-1947; 1202
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 01-07-1947 t/m 08-07-1947; 1203
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 09-07-1947 t/m 23-07-1947; 1204
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 24-07-1947 t/m 06-08-1947; 1205
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 07-08-1947 t/m 20-08-1947; 1206
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 21-08-1947 t/m 04-09-1947; 1207
      - Official transcript of AMT 2, case 4 against Oswald Pohl et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, Germany., 15-09-1947 t/m 03-11-1947; 1208
      - Supplement of Judgement., 11 aug. 1948; 1209
    - A.M.T. Court 2 case 9. against Otto Ohlendorf e.a., 47.5.
      - Indictment; openingstatement; closing statements diverse openingsreden en pleidooien voor afzonderlijke beklaagden., 1947/1948; 1210
      - Diverse openingsreden en pleidooien voor de afzonderlijke beklaagden (vervolg)., 1948; 1211
      - Diverse openingsreden en pleidooien voor de afzonderlijke beklaagden (vervolg)., 1947/1948; 1212
      - Zittingen van AMT 2 in de zaak tegen Otto Ohlendorf e.a., 17 okt 1947 8 t/m 10 apr, 1948; 1213
    - A.M.T. Court 3 case 3 against Josef Altstötter e.a., 47.6.
      - Indictment; opening-statement; 5 mrt. 1947, List of sources for the final plea for Cuhorst. Diverse correction sheets. 17,18 okt. 1947; 1214
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 17-02-1947 t/m 10-03-1947; 1215
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 11-03-1947 t/m 27-03-1947; 1216
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 28-03-1947 t/m 02-04-1947; 1217
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 03-04-1947 t/m 14-04-1947; 1218
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 15-04-1947 t/m 24-04-1947; 1219
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 28-04-1947 t/m 30-04-1947; 1220
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 01-05-1947 t/m 27-05-1947; 1221
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 28-05-1947 t/m 01-07-1947; 1222
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 02-07-1947 t/m 07-07-1947; 1223
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 08-07-1947 t/m 17-07-1947; 1224
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg. (die van 22 juli ook in Duits)., 18-07-1947 t/m 31-07-1947; 1225
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg (Die van 1 aug. ook in Duits)., 01-08-1947 t/m 06-08-1947; 1226
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 07-08-1947 t/m 13-08-1947; 1227
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 14-08-1947 t/m 27-08-1947; 1228
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 28-08-1947 t/m 11-09-1947; 1229
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 12-09-1947 t/m 16-09-1947; 1230
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 17-09-1947 t/m 24-09-1947; 1231
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 25-09-1947 t/m 16-10-1947; 1232
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 17-10-1947 t/m 18-10-1947; 1233
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 03-12-1947 t/m 04-12-1947; 1234
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Josef Altstötter, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg, doch in het Duits., 03-12-1947 t/m 04-12-1947; 1235
    - A.M.T. court 3. case 10 against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach e.a., 47.7.
      - Indictment., 16 aug. 1947; 1236
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 17-11-1947 t/m 15-12-1947; 1237
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 16-12-1947 t/m 09-01-1948; 1238
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 12-01-1948 t/m 14-00-1948; 1239
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 15-01-1948 t/m 23-01-1948; 1240
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 24-01-1948 t/m 03-02-1948; 1241
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 04-02-1948 t/m 12-02-1948; 1242
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 13-02-1948 t/m 19-02-1948; 1243
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 20-02-1948 t/m 22-03-1948; 1244
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 24-03-1948 t/m 21-04-1948; 1245
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 22-04-1948 t/m 03-05-1948; 1246
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 04-05-1948 t/m 11-05-1948; 1247
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 12 mei 1948; 1248
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 13-05-1948 t/m 15-05-1948; 1249
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 17-05-1948 t/m 21-05-1948; 1250
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 22,24 mei 1948; 1251
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 25,26 mei 1948; 1252
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 27-05-1948 t/m 01-06-1948; 1253
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 2, 3 juni 1948; 1254
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 4, 5 Juni 1948; 1255
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 07-06-1948 t/m 25-06-1948; 1256
      - Official transcripts of AMT 3 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Alfred Krupp von Bohlen und Halbach, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg. 27-06-1948 t/m 30-06-1948, Correctieboeken.; 12 febr. en 12 mrt. 1948; 1257
    - A.M.T. Court 4. case 5 against Friedrich Flick e.a., 47.8.
      - Documentbook, 1258
      - Indictment. Pleidooien in het proces tegen F. Flick e.a; Campanies and personalities associated with Friedrich Flick. nov. 1947, Openingstate-ment against F. Flick. 9 apr. 1947; Openingstatement für Bernhard Weiss. juli 1947; 1259
      - Slotpleidooien voor F. Flick en Konrad Kaletsch., 1260
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 15-03-1947 t/m 28-04-1947; 1261
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 29-04-1947 t/m 12-05-1947; 1262
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 13-05-1947 t/m 27-05-1947; 1263
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 28-05-1947 t/m 13-06-1947; 1264
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 02-07-1947 t/m 15-07-1947; 1265
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 16-07-1947 t/m 18-07-1947; 1266
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg.(Die van 23 juli ook in Duits), 21-07-1947 t/m 31-07-1947; 1267
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 01-08-1947 t/m 14-08-1947; 1268
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 15-08-1947 t/m 19-08-1947; 1269
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 02-09-1947 t/m 12-09-1947; 1270
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg. dooh in Duits. 12, 15 sept. 1947, Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg. 15-09-1947 t/m 24-09-1947; 1271
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 30-09-1947 t/m 16-10-1947; 1272
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 17-10-1947 t/m 31-10-1947; 1273
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 01-11-1947 t/m 04-11-1947; 1274
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 05-11-1947 t/m 26-11-1947; 1275
      - Official transcripts of AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Friedrich Flick, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 28-11-1947 t/m 22-12-1947; 1276
    - A.M.T. court 4, case 11 against Ernst von Weizsäcker e.a., 47.9.
      - Indictment., 15 nov. 1947; 1277
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 20-12-1947 t/m 09-01-1948; 1278
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 12-01-1948 t/m 04-02-1948; 1279
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 05-02-1948 t/m 10-02-1948; 1280
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 11-02-1948 t/m 19-02-1948; 1281
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 24-02-1948 t/m 11-03-1948; 1282
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 12-03-1948 t/m 22-03-1948; 1283